having no gaping hole, despite his beams being fireproofed and the whole slew of other flaws
in the NIST report, World Trade Center 7 also fell at free fall speed perfectly into its
footprint, making it only the third steel building to ever collapse from fire alongside
World Trade Center 1 and 2, the only three times in history, all in one day, all falling
the exact same way, despite all three of them being damaged in three different ways.
It's also a note that since only one other steel building has ever collapsed from fire
and that was the NIRAN, which if you observe, falls much more realistically asymmetrically.
Here's a side-by-side comparison.
Which one does World Trade Center 7 resemble?
And how are we even still discussing this two decades later?
You also have this interesting response from John Kerry when asked about Silverstein's
statement that he gave the order to, quote, Paul, Building 7.
Wow.
It takes weeks to months to prepare such a demolition.
The only way someone could make a decision to pull it and bring it down in a controlled
fashion would be if they had already been pre-rigged for demo.
And of course, everyone knew right away that it was terrorists, no need to do an investigation
of more than say, I don't know, half a day.